Paul Mulvaney

0851124394

paulmulvaney1@gmail.com



paulmulvaneydesign.com



2013

linkedin.com/in/paul-mulvaney-sligo/

About Me

UX/UI Designer with four years of experience in employment and study. Graduate of App Design & User Experience at ATU Sligo, with honours, looking to begin a new career opportunity that will allow me to fully utilize my skills and experiences, as well as challenge me continue to learn and grow in my career.

Skills

Design

Experienced with the following design software:

- Adobe XD
- Fiama
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Inkscape

Research

Experienced with the following UX research skills:

- User Testing
- A/B Testing
- User Flows
- Empathy Mapping
- Site Mapping
- Accessibility Analysis

Programming

Also experienced with programming in the following languages:

- HTML
- CSS/ Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- Python
- Express JS/ Node

References

References available on request

Education

Bachelor of Arts in App Design & User Experience

ATU Sligo 2020 - 2024

Gained Experience in all aspects of User Experience & User Interface design, from research through to final deliverables. Also studied UX content strategy and Accessibility. Worked on multiple clients led projects, such as Play 25 online and Gym Advisors, working directly with shareholders/ business owners to deliver final products.

It Support Specialist

MSLETB Sligo 2019 - 2020

Obtained Certification in CompTIA A+; Network+ & Security+

Furniture Making and Design

Sligo CFE 2013 – 2014

Leaving Certificate

Summerhill College, Sligo

Work Experience

User Experience Designer

Kudos Health 2023

Redesigning Kudos Health product range; Conducting research on existing services; Creating design prototypes; Building new design system guidelines; Collaborating and presenting to product owner and development teams.

Clinic Co-Ordinator

Hidden Hearing 2021

Full management of office; Scheduling and organising appointments; Managing deliveries; Stock ordering; Branch sales.

Customer Service Advisor

ATU Sligo 2018 - 2019

Listening to; understanding and resolving customer complaints; Understanding; Upgrading and selling company product range.

Sales Assistant

ATU Sligo 2016 - 2018

Serving customers and making product recommendations; Sales; Cash handling & store banking; Product testing; Visual merchandising; Monitoring and meeting store K.P.Is; Opening & closing store.

Freelance Work

Brand Designer & Graphic Designer

Sligo Chess Club 2022 - 2024

Branding Design; Including logo creation, colour palettes, typography and design guides; Creating branding elements including signage, social media posts, web design elements, and competition material for multiple competitions.